Max Gryaznov

Product Designer Portfolio LinkedIn verymoko@gmail.com +972 55 2718504, Haifa, Israel

I'm an analytical, creative interface designer with 2 years of experience with a background in racecar engineering and book design. I worked on B2B SaaS projects, creating wireframes, user flows. Skilled in web technologies to test and prototype own designs. I want to join an agency or a product, specializing in professional, complex, and social interfaces as a problem-solver and user-centered UX/UI designer.

Skills: Figma, Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Lightroom, Blender, Unity.

Experience

Product Designer in Smart Campus. Israel, remote

05/2023—present

School and educational management system. B2C.

- Developed the user interface for a web project management app for directors, workers, and interns.
- Enhanced the user experience, by designing the app for desktop, tablet, mobile, and printing.
- Accelerated the teamwork by expanding UI kit to a design system with specifications and guidelines.
- Optimized layouts and user flows with usability testing and feedback.

UX/UI Designer in DF Systems. Israel, remote

04/2022—06/2023

Startup focused on contract management and signature. B2B.

- Researched and identified users' needs and business goals.
- Designed user-friendly document management and signature system for event managers.
- Designed user experience for desktop and mobile plus layouts and controls for graphic editor.
- Envisioned collecting feedback from every user who completed the task.
- Executed all visual design stages from concept to high-fidelity mockups and code.

Web designer on Sravni.ru projects. Moscow, Russia. Remote

2021

Financial marketplace that helps to choose banks, insurance companies, and more.

- Designed the landing page of the half-year report, ensuring brand consistency
- Created the data visualization: chose and drew charts for desktop, tablet and mobile.
- Collaborated with project managers and developers, updated my design with team and users' feedback.
- Landing Page successfully attracted new customers.

Mechanical design engineer in GAZ. Nizhny Novgorod, Russia

01/2019—09/2021

Designed suspension and exterior parts for race trucks.

Education

UX and UI design, Sobaka Pavlova Certificates: 1, 2, 3, 4

Understanding user's needs, estimating deadlines, and creating interfaces of any complexity: from notification text to CMS, admin panels and graphic editors.

Frontend development, Masa

9-12/2021

JavaScript from basics to React and Node. Data types, arrays, functions, objects, classes.

Mechanical engineering specialist, specializing in automotive

2013-2018

Nizhny Novgorod State Technical university n.a. R.E. Alekseev.

Languages

Technologies

English working proficiency, Russian native, Hebrew elementary proficiency.

HTML, CSS, JS, d3js, C#.